zendough.com 2010-05-17

# zendough.com | Privacy Policy

Last updated May 4, 2010.

### The Information We Collect from You

zendough allows you to access the zendough product through our Web site. We collect your personal information only if you decide to purchase zendough, subscribe to our newsletter, or surveys or transact other business with us. In order to process your transactions and provide you with quality customer service, we need your full name  
and current and/or billing address, your email address (so we can contact you) and, if you purchase one of our products, a valid credit card number, your Social Security number and certain other personal information, such as your date of birth, address information, employment information, and certain credit card and loan account information. We use personal information to authenticate the credit card number and to confirm that the person requesting your credit report as part of zendough really is you and not an impostor or other person improperly seeking to access your information.

### What Security Measures We Take

zendough takes precautions to secure your personal information. If and when we ask you to provide your personal information, we will do so through a Web page that uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. This protocol provides security for your information by encrypting it as it travels from your computer to our computer. We then move all of the personal information that we collect or obtain about you, including your credit report, to a special computer for security purposes by means of a one-way transfer on our proprietary network. This special computer is not connected to the Internet, and zendough has controls in place to limit access to and secure the data maintained therein.

### How We Use and Share Your Personal Information

If you indicate to us that you are interested in receiving information regarding other products and services from zendough and third party partners, your name, e-mail address and other registration information may be shared with a third party in order to present these offers to you. Personal information that is shared with these entities will be monitored in accordance with our security and confidentiality policies. If you prefer not to receive such information, you may indicate your preference by marking the appropriate box when you register, place an order or update your account information, and zendough will not send you any promotional materials.

### Emails

When you order zendough, we will email you a receipt of your purchase. The zendough product also includes alert emails that are sent on a daily, weekly or monthly basis. These emails are part of the zendough benefits and cannot be disabled for persons who are zendough members.

### Ordering

When you order zendough or other product or service, zendough must share some of your personal information with third parties in order to process your transaction. For example, zendough must share your name, address and social security number with one or more of the major credit reporting agencies in order to obtain your requested credit reports, and must share your name, address and credit card account number with our credit card processing partner in order to process your payment. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

### Third Parties

If you indicated to us when you registered, placed an order or updated your account that you were interested in receiving information about products and services provided by zendough, and its third party marketing partners your name, email address and other registration information may be shared with a third party in order to present these offers to you. These entities are only allowed to use shared information for the intended purpose only and will be monitored in accordance with our security and confidentiality policies. In the event you indicate that you want to receive personalized offers from zendough based on information from your credit profile, your credit information may be used to serve relevant ads to you when you visit the site and provide other relevant offers from zendough based on such information. zendough also may disclose your personal information to third parties in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with, or be responsive to, legal process served on us (such as a subpoena), or if we believe such disclosure is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of zendough, our users or others. In addition, we may disclose your personal information to consultants, agents and advisors, such as attorneys and accountants, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is within the scope of their professional duties to zendough and with the understanding that such professionals will abide by our security and confidentiality policies. In the event that you unsubscribe from email communications, we may share your email address with our compliance agents or approved marketing partners to prevent you from receiving additional offers.

### The Collection of Anonymous Data

In order to enhance the usefulness of our Web site and our products and services, zendough will collect data about our customers' use of our Web site, in a manner that does not include any personally identifiable information. While you browse the zendough Web site, we note which pages of our site you visit and note the IP address of your computer (as all Web sites do automatically), but we do not link that address information to your personal information for marketing purposes but may for the purpose of product delivery. The general information we gather enables us to serve our customers better by continually enhancing our site based on up-to-date use patterns.

### Information Regarding Your Subscription

We may use information about your zendough subscription, such as your usage patterns, to customize your web site and/or customer service experience.

### Updating Your Personal Information and Email Preferences

You can correct or update at any time the personal information that you provided and that we maintain on you by accessing the zendough Web site and selecting "Profile" then “My Information.” You can also indicate your preference not to receive promotional offers from “Profile” then “Preferences”. zendough is not responsible for and cannot amend the information in your credit report, which is produced by one or more credit reporting agencies. If you believe that some of the information in your credit report is inaccurate, you must contact the applicable credit reporting agency directly.

### zendough Newsletter

You may sign up for our free monthly newsletter in one of two ways. First, you may enter your email address in the "Free Newsletter" field on our homepage, or on an affiliate's page. Second, our newsletter will be emailed to you if you select the offers zendough opt-in box during the ordering process. If you entered your email address into a " Free Newsletter" field, you can opt-out of receiving the email by responding to the newsletter and asking to be unsubscribed, or calling our customer service department and asking to be taken off the list. If you signed up for our newsletter by selecting the offers opt-in box during the ordering process, you may unsubscribe through the above two processes, or you may go to www.zendough.com, log-in as a member, click on the "Profile” link then select “Preferences", and de-select the offers opt-in box.

### Notification of Changes to this Privacy Statement

zendough may amend this Privacy Statement at any time, and without advance notice. We recommend that from time to time you review this Privacy Statement to check for changes.

### Possible Acquisition

In the event of an acquisition of all or part of zendough by another company, or in the event that zendough were to sell or dispose of all or a part of the business, the acquirer would have access to the information maintained by the zendough business, which could include your personal information, subject to applicable law. The acquirer's privacy policy might be different than zendough's privacy policy, or the acquirer might choose to amend zendough's privacy policy. You will be notified by email if, as a result of such acquisition, zendough's privacy policy is materially changed or if the acquirer's privacy policy is materially different than zendough's privacy policy. In connection with such notice, you will be given an opportunity to inform the acquirer that you do not consent to the use or disclosure by the acquirer of your personal information in accordance with such new or revised privacy policy.

If you would like at any time to review our then-current Privacy Statement, please visit http://www.zendough.com/zendough/help.zh?hp=pp.

### The Use of Cookies

zendough uses "cookies," which are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes, to facilitate your access to our products and services. zendough uses cookies in accordance with industry-standard protocols, and does not use cookies, either directly or in conjunction with other Web sites, to track your movement to Web sites other than zendough. If you would like more information about cookies, you can visit <http://www.cookiecentral.com/n_cookie_faq.htm>. zendough uses two different types of cookies. One type of cookie is used so that our site "recognizes" you each time you return using the same computer, and you do not have to re-enter all your personal information on each visit. You can set your Web browser to refuse to accept this cookie, or delete this type of cookie from your hard drive, and still access our products and services, as long as you re-enter information each time you visit. The second type of cookie is needed so that we can process each step of your transactions with us. If you refuse to accept this type of cookie, you will not be able to access our products and services. Most Web browsers automatically delete this type of cookie when you terminate your session.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our site or on other sites which we use for advertising. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness; and they are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

### Links to Other Web Sites

Some pages on the zendough Web site may contain links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

### Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. zendough will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. zendough does not store this information; it is used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

### Policy Regarding Children

We define children as individuals under the age of 16. Our Web Site is not intended for the use of children and we do not intend to collect information about children through our Web Site. You must be at least 18 to access any products through this website or to join zendough as a member entitled to membership benefits.

### zendough

zendough is a trade name of TransUnion Interactive, Inc., a Delaware corporation based in San Luis Obispo, California.
